[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Edward Nigma was the name of which fictional character?", "correct_answer": "The Riddler", "incorrect_answers": ["Friday", "Professor  Moraiarity", "The  Joker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Human beings have 23 pairs of  chromosomes. Which animal has the most chromosomes?", "correct_answer": "hermit crabs", "incorrect_answers": ["minke whale", "millipedes", "elephants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word is used  to signify a style of animation developed and advanced by Japanese animators.", "correct_answer": "anime", "incorrect_answers": ["nimthal", "phoeme", "mangal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kate Beckinsale, Scott Speedman and Shane Brolly star in the 2003 movie Underworld.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "News woman Veronica Corningstone from the movie Anchorman was played by actress Christina Applegate.  In what groundbreaking Fox TV sitcom did she make her starring debut?", "correct_answer": "Married...With Children", "incorrect_answers": ["In Living Color", "Hermans Head", "The Tracy Ullman Show"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city was the first , free, public high school opened?", "correct_answer": "Boston", "incorrect_answers": ["Orono", "Charleston", "Philadelphia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous Latin maxim, which is the official motto of South Carolina, means While I breathe, I hope.", "correct_answer": "Dum spiro spero", "incorrect_answers": ["Si quaeris peninsulam amoenam circumspice", "Nil sine numine", "Salus populi suprema lex esto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What place has the maximum amount of sunshine in the US?", "correct_answer": "Yuma, Arizona", "incorrect_answers": ["Anchorage, Alaska", "Houston, Texas", "St Petersburg, Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters from the 1984 movie The Karate Kid, was NOT a member of the Cobra Kai?", "correct_answer": "Freddy", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby", "Johnny", "Tommy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these methods is used in traditional Chinese medicine to diagnose conditions and diseases?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Listening to the patients voice", "Exploring the patients body odors", "Checking the patients hair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Kiefer Sutherlands character in the 1986 film Stand by Me?", "correct_answer": "Ace", "incorrect_answers": ["Gordy", "Teddy", "Denny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrecked the family car in Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Biff", "incorrect_answers": ["Jennifer", "Marty", "George"]}]